[
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1700730355,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1700730355",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1700730355,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"ceg&#322;a\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"brick\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 863209271,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 863209271",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 863209271,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"cennik\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"price list<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1335918013,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1335918013",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1335918013,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"ch&#281;tny\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"willing\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1086409842,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1086409842",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1086409842,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"chodnik\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"pavement\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 555648120,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 555648120",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 555648120,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"chowa&#263;\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"hide\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1545132808,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1545132808",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1545132808,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"chwali&#263; si&#281;<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"broast\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1864884236,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1864884236",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1864884236,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"sk&#261;py<br><br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"mean\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1105363415,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1105363415",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1105363415,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"przebieg&#322;y\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"cunning\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 821726095,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 821726095",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 821726095,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"ci&#261;g\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"series\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1030003385,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1030003385",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1030003385,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"ciep&#322;o\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"warmth, heat<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1800264050,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1800264050",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1800264050,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"cierpie&#263;\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"suffer\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 294613284,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 294613284",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 294613284,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"c&#322;o\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"duty\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 834047919,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 834047919",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 834047919,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"cud <br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"miracle\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1409995472,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1409995472",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1409995472,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"cyfra\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"number\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1967795410,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1967795410",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1967795410,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"czajnik\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"kettle\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1158638058,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1158638058",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1158638058,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"czar (zakl&#281;cie)\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"spell\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1282832830,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1282832830",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1282832830,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"czepek (k&#261;pielowy)<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"bathing cap<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1894235048,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1894235048",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1894235048,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"czo&#322;o\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"forehead\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1061688391,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1061688391",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1061688391,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\".czu&#322;y (serdeczny)<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"tender\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 333438798,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 333438798",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 333438798,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"be on the alert<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"czuwa&#263;\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1820674686,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1820674686",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1820674686,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"czynsz\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"rent\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 1409133309,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 1409133309",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 1409133309,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"d&#261;&#380;y&#263;\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"to aim at,<br>to aspire<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 809529188,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 809529188",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 809529188,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"deptak\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"promenade\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 2085886329,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 2085886329",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 2085886329,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"deska (gruba),<br>deska (cienka)<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"board<br>plank<br>\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  },
  {
    "courseId": 46945,
    "number": 506201049,
    "type": 0,
    "name": "Page 506201049",
    "disabled": false,
    "contentType": 3,
    "tag": "",
    "lockedBy": 0,
    "level": "",
    "keywords": "",
    "backgroundUrl": null,
    "content": {
      "courseId": 46945,
      "pageNumber": 506201049,
      "lessonTitle": "",
      "chapterTitle": "",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "question": "{\"content\":\"dno\",\"media\":[]}",
      "answer": "{\"content\":\"bottom\",\"media\":[]}",
      "questionTitleEn": "",
      "questionEn": "",
      "answerEn": "",
      "speech": null
    },
    "template": null,
    "interaction": null,
    "courseName": "My MemoCards",
    "modified": 737666,
    "files": [],
    "typeEnum": "EXERCISE",
    "contentTypeEnum": "JSON"
  }
]